# Shafiqul Bari Sadman

# Software Engineer

Having 3+ years of experience in software industry with track record of working in different project and organization which helped me to adopt to the changes quickly and made me a mature team worker. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative and able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadline.

- ★ shafiqulbarisadman@gmail.com
- Kuala lumpur, Malaysia
- S live:.cid.80d829edfde32d8f

- +60143404952
- in linkedin.com/in/sadman6259
- github.com/sadman6259

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer Accenture

11/2022 - Present

Responsibilities

 Design and develop solution for highly scalable and secured banking solution.

Kuala lumpur, Malaysia

 Fix existing bugs, collaborate with testing team for betterment of features.

# Software Engineer

# Surbana Jurong Private Limited

01/2022 - 10/2022

Responsibilities

 Requirement analysis, design and develop solution for high volume of data driven IOT based project.

 Work in Every steps of project management from initial layout designing to database design.

# Software Engineer

# Labaid pharmaceutical Limited

04/2021 - 12/2021

Responsibilities

 Build new modules for ERP System to manage business for a large pharmaceutical company.

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Remote

 Build a new application from scratch to manage order and sales of a company.

# Software Engineer (Part-time) **XTRATECH**

08/2021 - 04/2022

Remote

Responsibilites

 Integrate different 3rd party API's (Turkish airlines, Travellanda etc) for travel technology app which is responsible for flight and hotel booking.

 Implement better solution for tuning performance of existing solutions and fix bugs.

# **Junior Software Engineer** PiisTech

11/2019 - 03/2021

Responsibilities

 Build New modules for a CRM as per client requirements and fix existing bugs of the system.

Dhaka, Bangladesh

 Directly work with team lead and write efficient code and query to manage business deals

# **SKILLS**



# **PROJECTS**

## UOB Wealth Management System (11/2022 - Present)

 .NET Based web application for managing customers wealth for UOB Bank. it's a large, highly scalable and secured application. It also uses different 3rd party and external services integration.

# Sustainable Building Management (01/2022 - 10/2022)

 IOT Project Built in .NET web api and in front end AngularJS to manage building performance like it measures performance of Water, Electricity, Waste, Indoor Air Quality etc. Here I have to deal with large volume of data and various custom charts to visualize data.

# Labaid ERP (04/2021 - 12/2021)

 ERP system built in. NET Core Web api and Angular for managing organization business.It covers the whole process in business operation like HRMS,SCM,PPIC,SALES,PMD,Quality Control, INVENTORY etc.

#### Depot Management System (06/2021 - 12/2021)

.NET Core Web Api and Angular based web application for manage products sales and corresponsing process. It has Features like Invoice, Allocation, Summary, Collection, Stock, Bank deposit

### RMR CLOUD (12/2019 - 02/2021)

Accounting and Customer Management Application built in .NET Core Web Api, Angular . It included features like Customer, Lead, Invoice, Inventory, Tickets, Sales, Estimates, Estimat or, Reports etc.

# **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor In Computer Science

Patuakhali Science & Technology University (Patuakhali, Bangladesh) (01/2016 - 12/2019)

# **ACHIEVEMENT**

Solve problems in different online platforms

Participated in Hackathon